You must understand though the touch of your hand
Makes my pulse react
That it's only the thrill of boy meeting girl
Opposites attract
It's physical
Only logical
You must try to ignore that
it means more than that
What's love got to do, got to do with it?
What's love but a second-hand emotion?
Who needs a heart when a heart can be broken?
It may seem to you that I'm acting confused
When you're close to me
If I tend to look dazed I've read it someplace
I've got cause to be
There's a name for it
There's a phrase that fits
But whatever the reason you do it for me
What's love got to do, got to do with it?
What's love but a second-hand emotion?
Who needs a heart when a heart can be broken?
I've been taking on a new direction
But I have to say
I've been thinking about my own protection
It scares me to feel this way
What's love got to do, got to do with it?
What's love but a second-hand emotion?
Who needs a heart when a heart can be broken?
What's love got to do, got to do with it?
What's love but a sweet old-fashioned notion?
Who needs a heart when a heart can be broken?
What's love got to do
Got to do with it
What's love but a second-hand emotion?
What's love got to do, got to do with it?
Who needs a heart when a heart can be broken